Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - P
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - The other woman, 1982; SR-23113; Parker, Ray, Jr. (Box 384)
          Arista
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - The other woman, 1982; SR-23114; Parker, Ray, Jr. (Box 384)
          Catalog # 600 619; A-side Matrix # 600619 A-1/82S I
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - I don't think that man should sleep alone, 1987; SR-23115; Parker, Ray, Jr. (Box 384)
          Catalog # 0-20636; A-side Matrix # 0-20636-A-SH1 O B-28483-SH1 1-1
          Geffen Records
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - It's time to party now, 1980; SR-23116; Parker, Ray, Jr.; Raydio (Box 384)
          Catalog # SP-102; A-side Matrix # 1T SP102-SA CT1
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - It's your night, 1981; SR-23117; Parker, Ray, Jr.; Raydio (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23118. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # SP-113; A-side Matrix # T1 SP113-SAL-T2
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - It's your night, 1981; SR-23118; Parker, Ray, Jr.; Raydio (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23117. 2 copies. Promo
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - The other woman, 1982; SR-23119; Parker, Ray, Jr. (Box 384)
          Catalog # ARIST 12 466; A-side Matrix # ARISTA 12466 A
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - Ghostbusters, 1984; SR-23120; Parker, Ray, Jr. (Box 384)
          Catalog # ADP-9223; A-side Matrix # ADP 9223-A
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - She needs to get some, 1991; SR-23121; Parker, Ray, Jr.; Father MC (Box 384)
          Catalog # MCA12 54115; A-side Matrix # MCA-10814 FDS-1
        - Parker, Ray, Jr. - Two places at the same time, 1980; SR-23122; Parker, Ray, Jr.; Raydio (Box 384)
          Catalog # AL 9515; A-side Matrix # T1 AL-9515-SA (RE-1)-CTH-2
        - Parks, Leslie - Body heat, 1987; SR-23123; Parks, Leslie (Box 384)
          Catalog # TGR-1020; A-side Matrix # TGR-1020-A
        - Parliament - Funkentelechy vs. the placebo syndrome, 1977; SR-23124; Parliament (Box 384)
          Catalog # NBLP 7084; A-side Matrix # T1 NBLP-7084-AS TH-3
          Casablanca
        - Parliament - Live "81", 1981; SR-23125; Parliament; Funkadelic (Box 384)
          Catalog # FRC 102; A-side Matrix # L 33391 PF-1
          Funk Record Co.
        - Parliament - Funk mastercuts, 1985; SR-23126; Parliament; Parlet; Bootsy's Rubber Band (Box 384)
          Catalog # FR-2152; A-side Matrix # FR-2152-A A
          Funk Mastercuts
        - Parliament - GloryHallaStoopid (pin the tale on the funky), 1979; SR-23127; Parliament; Clinton, George (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23128. 2 copies.
          Catalog # NBLP 7195; A-side Matrix # A-1 NBLP-7195-AS K-2
        - Parliament - GloryHallaStoopid (pin the tale on the funky), 1979; SR-23128; Parliament; Clinton, George (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23127. 2 copies.
        - Parliament - Crush it; Body language, 1980; SR-23129; Parliament; Clinton, George; Collins, Bootsy (Box 384)
          Catalog # NBD 20235 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20235-AS PW
        - Parliament - Agony of defeet, 1980; SR-23130; Parliament; Clinton, George (Box 384)
          Catalog # NBD 20232 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20232-DJ-AS-RE C1-1
        - Parliament - Parliament's greatest hits, 1984; SR-23131; Parliament (Box 384)
          Catalog # 422-822 637-1 M-1; A-side Matrix # 422-822-637-1-AS-PRC-R-1-2-1
        - Parliament - Dope dogs (disc one), 1995; SR-23132; Parliament; Funkadelic; P-Funk All Stars (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23133. Double album.
          Catalog # HOTH LP 1; A-side Matrix # HOTHLP 1 A-1-1-1
          Hot Hands
        - Parliament - Dope dogs (disc two), 1995; SR-23133; Parliament; Funkadelic; P-Funk All Stars (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23132. Double album.
          Catalog # HOTH LP 1; A-side Matrix # HOTHLP 1 C-1-1-
        - Parrish, Man - Brown sugar, 1987; SR-23134; Parrish, Man (Box 384)
          Catalog # FMS 62282; A-side Matrix # FMS62282 A RE
          Select Records
        - Parrish, Man - Man parrish, 1982; SR-23135; Parrish, Man (Box 384)
          Catalog # MP-320; A-side Matrix # MP-320-1
          Importe/12
        - Parrish, Man - Hip hop be bop (don't stop), 1996; SR-23136; Parrish, Man; Freeze Force (Box 384)
          Catalog # HCL 2294; A-side Matrix # HCL-2294-A
          Hot Classics
          Miami, Florida
        - Part Time Christians - Rock and roll is disco, 1984; SR-23137; Part Time Christians (Box 384)
          Catalog # VIRUS 40; A-side Matrix # VIRUS 40 A L-18925
          Alternative Tentacles
        - Partido Em 5 - Vol. 1, 1983; SR-23138; Partido Em 5 (Box 384)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # 803.383; A-side Matrix # 306.8024-A
          Tapecar
          Brazil
        - Partland Brothers - Soul city, 1987; SR-23139; Partland Brothers (Box 384)
          Catalog # V-56060; A-side Matrix # V156060-241309-D-Z1
          Manhattan Records
        - Parris - Never take your love, 1980; SR-23140; Parris (Box 384)
          Catalog # D 214; A-side Matrix # 7-1024-1A
          Brunswick
          New York, United States
        - Partner In Crime - Do you know what I'm saying; Mary, Mary, 1988; SR-23141; Partner In Crime; Easy El Gee (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23142. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # CR 12-024; A-side Matrix # CR 12 024 SLAM
          Criminal Records
        - Partner In Crime - Do you know what I'm saying; Mary, Mary, 1988; SR-23142; Partner In Crime; Easy El Gee (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23141. 2 copies. Promo
        - Partner In Crime - Do you know what I'm saying; Mary, Mary, 1988; SR-23143; Partner In Crime; Easy El Gee (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23144. Different discs. Promo
        - Partner In Crime - Do you know what I'm saying; Mary, Mary, 1988; SR-23144; Partner In Crime; Easy El Gee (Box 384)
          In same jacket as # SR-23143. Different discs.Test Pressing
        - Partners - Chante; Pouki sa, 1988; SR-23145; Partners (Box 384)
          Catalog # RFE 6503; A-side Matrix # RFE-SP-001 A
          R. Francis Entertainment
        - Partners - Chante; Pouki sa, 1988; SR-23146; Partners (Box 384)
        - Partners - Give it to me all night long; Love pains (special DJ edited version), 1982; SR-23147; Partners; Elliman, Yvonne (Box 384)
          Catalog # BTG-1232; A-side Matrix # BTG-1232-A1
          Moby Dick Records
        - Partners-N-Crime - Pump tha party (puttin' in work), 1995; SR-23148; Partners-N-Crime; Prime Time (Box 384)
          Catalog # BB019; A-side Matrix # BB-0019-LP A
          Big Boy Records
          New Orleans, Louisiana
        - Parton, Dolly - Potential new boyfriend, 1983; SR-23149; Parton, Dolly (Box 384)
          Catalog # JW 13545; A-side Matrix # PW-13545-A
          RCA
        - Parts Unknown - Make u famous, 2005; SR-23150; Parts Unknown (Box 384)
          Catalog # FJ12004; A-side Matrix # FJ 12004 A
          Fatt Jointz Records
        - Party, Alex - Don't give me your life, 1995; SR-23151; Party, Alex (Box 384)
          Catalog # 697 120 071-1; A-side Matrix # 697-120-071-1 A
          FFRR
        - Party Brigade - Everybody shake it up, 1995; SR-23152; Party Brigade (Box 384)
          Catalog # DBT-1124; A-side Matrix # DBT-1124 A
          Dance Baby Records
        - Pas De Deux - Je t'aime, 1998; SR-23153; Pas De Deux; Robinson, Windsor (Box 384)
          Catalog # SAMPMS 5565; A-side Matrix # 12.5565 20 1A1
          Columbia
        - Pasadenas - Another lover, 1991; SR-23154; Pasadenas (Box 384)
          Catalog # 656845 6; A-side Matrix # 31-656845-20-1A-1
        - Passion - Gigolos get lonely too (1996 players version), 1996; SR-23155; Passion (Box 384)
          Catalog # MCA12 55237; A-side Matrix # MCA 12642-RDS-1
        - Passion - Gigolos get lonely too (1996 players version), 1996; SR-23156; Passion (Box 384)
        - Passion - Where I'm from, 1996; SR-23157; Passion (Box 384)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3471; A-side Matrix # MCA12536-1
        - Passion - Where I'm from, 1996; SR-23158; Passion (Box 384)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3716; A-side Matrix # (MCA8P-3716A) MCA-12571
        - Passion - Gigolos get lonely too (1996 players version), 1996; SR-23159; Passion (Box 384)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3796; A-side Matrix # MCA 12622-RDS-1
        - Passion - Where I'm from, 1996; SR-23160; Passion (Box 384)
        - Passion Fodder - Luz blanca (Spoons mix), 1986; SR-23161; Passion Fodder (Box 384)
          Catalog # 885 386-1; A-side Matrix # 222 885386 1 // 1 380
        - Passions - Sanctuary, 1982; SR-23162; Passions (Box 384)
          Catalog # 2383 641; A-side Matrix # 160 2383641 1 380
        - Passport - Looking thru, 1974; SR-23163; Passport (Box 385)
          Catalog # SD 7042; A-side Matrix # ST-C-743061-A
          ATCO Records
        - Passport - Man in the mirror, 1983; SR-23164; Passport (Box 385)
          Catalog # 80144-1; A-side Matrix # STA-835377-A B-18956-A
          Atlantic
        - Passport - Running in real time, 1985; SR-23165; Passport (Box 385)
          Catalog # 81251-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-855659-B 1-2 B-21196-B
        - Passport - Doldinger Jubilee '75, 1975; SR-23166; Passport; McCann, Les; Catherine, Philip (Box 385)
          Catalog # SD 18162; A-side Matrix # ST-A-753521-A
        - Passport - Earthborn, 1982; SR-23167; Passport (Box 385)
          Catalog # 80034-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A 825043A
        - Passport - Infinity machine, 1976; SR-23168; Passport (Box 385)
          Catalog # SD 36-132; A-side Matrix # ST-C-763565-AAA-1
        - Passport - Heavy nights, 1986; SR-23169; Passport (Box 385)
          Catalog # 81727-1; A-side Matrix # ST A866257A 1-1
        - Passport - Cross-collateral, 1975; SR-23170; Passport (Box 385)
          Catalog # SD 36-107; A-side Matrix # ST-C-743287-A
        - Pastor Troy - Are we cuttin', 2002; SR-23171; Pastor Troy; Miss Jade; Timbaland (Box 385)
          In same jacket as # SR-23172. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 440 019 167-1; A-side Matrix # 440-019-167-1A
          Universal Records
        - Pastor Troy - Are we cuttin', 2002; SR-23172; Pastor Troy; Miss Jade; Timbaland (Box 385)
          In same jacket as # SR-23171. 2 copies.
        - Pastor Troy - No mo play, 1999; SR-23173; Pastor Troy (Box 385)
          Catalog # U8P 1561; A-side Matrix # U8P-1561-ARE1
        - Pastor Troy - No mo play, 1999; SR-23174; Pastor Troy (Box 385)
        - Pastor Troy - No mo play, 1999; SR-23175; Pastor Troy (Box 385)
        - Patra - Romantic call, 1993; SR-23176; Patra; Yo-Yo (Box 385)
          Catalog # EAS 6438; A-side Matrix # XSS-6438-A-1A
          Epic
        - Patra - Bull daga gal, 1993; SR-23177; Patra; Lady Patra (Box 385)
          Catalog # 9051; A-side Matrix # 9051-A
          Shang Muzik
        - Patra - Pull up to the bumper, 1995; SR-23178; Patra (Box 385)
          Catalog # ABD 7193; A-side Matrix # XSS7193A-1A
          550 Music
        - Patra - Pull up to the bumper, 1995; SR-23179; Patra (Box 385)
        - Patra - Hard core, 1992; SR-23180; Patra (Box 385)
          Catalog # EAS 5135; A-side Matrix # XSS-5135A
        - Patra - Queen of the pack, 1993; SR-23181; Patra (Box 385)
          Catalog # E 53763; A-side Matrix # E-53763-2 A
        - Patra - Pull up to the bumper; Whining skill, 1995; SR-23182; Patra (Box 385)
          Catalog # BAS 7111; A-side Matrix # XSS-7111A
        - Patra - Pull up to the bumper; Whining skill, 1995; SR-23183; Patra (Box 385)
        - Patra - Think (about it), 1993; SR-23184; Patra; Collins, Lyn (Box 385)
          Catalog # 49 77075; A-side Matrix # 49-77075A-2
        - Patra - Think (about it), 1993; SR-23185; Patra; Collins, Lyn (Box 385)
        - Patra - Free di youth; Teach the children, 1994; SR-23186; Patra; Rebel, Tony (Box 385)
          Catalog # AED 6707; A-side Matrix # XSS-6707-A-1A
        - Patra - Free di youth; Teach the children, 1994; SR-23187; Patra; Rebel, Tony (Box 385)
        - Patterns In Peru - This is the night, 1986; SR-23188; Patterns In Peru (Box 385)
          Catalog # YZ60T; A-side Matrix # YZ60TA
          Vernon Bros
          England
        - Patterson, Bobby - Groove me, 1983; SR-23189; Patterson, Bobby (Box 385)
          Catalog # MAL-1210; A-side Matrix # MAL 1210A-1 A
          Malaco Records
          Jackson, Mississippi
        - Patterson, Rahsaan - It's alright now, 1999; SR-23190; Patterson, Rahsaan (Box 385)
          Catalog # MCAR 25034-1; A-side Matrix # OASIS DISC MASTERING MCA 13676
        - Patterson, Rahsaan - Treat you like a queen, 1999; SR-23191; Patterson, Rahsaan (Box 385)
          Catalog # MCA8P 4437; A-side Matrix # OASIS DISC MASTERING MCA 13596 (SIDE A)
        - Patterson, Rahsaan - Stop by, 1996; SR-23192; Patterson, Rahsaan (Box 385)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3849; A-side Matrix # MCA-12677-B6-1
        - Patterson, Rahsaan - Love in stereo, 1999; SR-23193; Patterson, Rahsaan (Box 385)
          Catalog # MCA1P-93059; A-side Matrix # OASIS DISC MASTERING MCA 13594 RE1 (SIDE A)
        - Patterson, Rahsaan - Love in stereo, 1999; SR-23194; Patterson, Rahsaan (Box 385)
        - Patti, Guesch - Labyrinthe, 1988; SR-23195; Patti, Guesch (Box 385)
          Catalog # 064-79 0563 1; A-side Matrix # 7905631-A1
          Pathé Marconi EMI
        - Patti, Guesch - Labyrinthe, 1988; SR-23196; Patti, Guesch (Box 385)
          Catalog # 7905631; A-side Matrix # 790563 1 A 2 M6 359295 2
        - Patti, Guesch - Let be must the queen, 1988; SR-23197; Patti, Guesch (Box 385)
          In same jacket as # SR-23198. 2 copies.
          Catalog # K 060-15 9832 6; A-side Matrix # 1598326-A1
        - Patti, Guesch - Let be must the queen, 1988; SR-23198; Patti, Guesch (Box 385)
          In same jacket as # SR-23197. 2 copies.
        - Patton, Tamika - Number one; No more lonely nights; Your precious love, 1990; SR-23200; Patton, Tamika (Box 385)
          Catalog # SPRO 04550; A-side Matrix # SPRO-04550-Z2
          Orpheus Records
        - Paul, Billy - It's critical; Bring the family back, 1979; SR-23201; Paul, Billy (Box 385)
          Catalog # 2Z8 3678; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AA-2Z8-3678-3
          Philadelphia International Records
        - Paul Boy - Lucky guy, 1988; SR-23202; Paul Boy (Box 385)
          Catalog # TA 001; A-side Matrix # TA 001 A
          Twist Again Records
        - Paul Cacia Band - Saved by your love, 1978; SR-23203; Paul Cacia Band; Cameo, Janine (Box 385)
          In same jacket as # SR-23204. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ALX 108; A-side Matrix # ALX-108-RE1
          Alexander Street Records
          Sherman Oaks, California
        - Paul Cacia Band - Saved by your love, 1978; SR-23204; Paul Cacia Band; Cameo, Janine (Box 385)
          In same jacket as # SR-23203. 2 copies.
        - Paul, Cameron - Mixx-it 22, 1988; SR-23205; Paul, Cameron; Tone Loc (Box 385)
          Catalog # CP-22; A-side Matrix # CP 22 A
          Mixx-it
          San Mateo, California
        - Paul, Cameron - Loops volume 3, 1992; SR-23206; Paul, Cameron (Box 385)
          Catalog # CPL3; A-side Matrix # CPL-3A
        - Paul, Cameron - Beats and pieces volume 5, 1991; SR-23207; Paul, Cameron (Box 385)
          Catalog # CPBP-5; A-side Matrix # PAP CPBP-5-A-G1A
        - Paul, Cameron - Loops volume 6, 1993; SR-23208; Paul, Cameron (Box 385)
          Catalog # CPL-6; A-side Matrix # CPL-6 A2
        - Paul, Cameron - Loops volume 6, 1993; SR-23209; Paul, Cameron (Box 385)
        - Paul, Cameron - Beats and pieces volume 7, 1992; SR-23210; Paul, Cameron (Box 385)
          Catalog # CPBP-7; A-side Matrix # CPBP-7 A2
        - Paul, Cameron - Beats and pieces volume 8, 1992; SR-23211; Paul, Cameron (Box 385)
          Catalog # CPBP-8; A-side Matrix # CPBP-8 A1
        - Paul, Chris - Back in my arms in the ghost house, 1988; SR-23212; Paul, Chris; House Engineers (Box 385)
          Catalog # 1C K 060-2 02462 6; A-side Matrix # 2024626-A1
          EMI Electrola
        - Paul, Frankie - Give me that feeling, 1987; SR-23213; Paul, Frankie (Box 385)
          Catalog # MR 1004; A-side Matrix # MR-1004-A1
          Moodies Records
          Bronx, New York
        - Paul, Frankie - Worries in the dance, 1987; SR-23214; Paul, Frankie (Box 385)
          Catalog # VPRD 172; A-side Matrix # VPRD 172-A
          Volcano
          Queens, New York
        - Paul, Leston - Eruption, 1987; SR-23215; Paul, Leston; New York Connection (Box 386)
          Catalog # BSR-LP-073; A-side Matrix # BSR-LP-073-A
          B's Records
        - Paul, Leston - Soca destruction, 1986; SR-23216; Paul, Leston; New York Connection (Box 386)
          Catalog # BSR-LP-050; A-side Matrix # BSR-LP 050-A
        - Paul, Leston - For real - Carnival hits '95, 1995; SR-23217; Paul, Leston; New York Connection (Box 386)
          Catalog # JW-069; A-side Matrix # JW-069-A LP LESTON PAUL
          JW Productions
        - Paul, Leston - Soca invasion II, 1988; SR-23218; Paul, Leston; New York Connection (Box 386)
          Catalog # JW-005; A-side Matrix # JW-LP-005-A
        - Paul, Leston - Soca invasion II, 1988; SR-23219; Paul, Leston; New York Connection (Box 386)
        - Paul, Leston - Party on fire, 1989; SR-23220; Paul, Leston; New York Connection (Box 386)
          Catalog # JW-025; A-side Matrix # JWLP 025-A LESTON PAUL 89 VDCM
        - Paul, Sean - Give it up to me; Never gonna be the same, 2006; SR-23221; Paul, Sean (Box 386)
          Catalog # PR 302219; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302219A-1 RJ
        - Paul, Sean - (When you gonna) give it up to me; Never gonna be the same, 2006; SR-23222; Paul, Sean; Cole, Keyshia (Box 386)
          Catalog # PR 302287; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302287A-1 RJ
        - Paul, Sean - The trinity, 2005; SR-23223; Paul, Sean (Box 386)
          In same jacket as # SR-23224. Double album.
          Catalog # 83788-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83788A1 RJ
        - Paul, Sean - The trinity, 2005; SR-23224; Paul, Sean (Box 386)
          In same jacket as # SR-23223. Double album.
          Catalog # 83788-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83788C-1 RJ
        - Paul, Sean - Temperature; Breakout, 2005; SR-23225; Paul, Sean (Box 386)
          Catalog # PR 302056; A-side Matrix # ST-A-94133A-1 RJ
        - Paul, Sean - Like glue, 2002; SR-23226; Paul, Sean (Box 386)
          Catalog # PR 301160; A-side Matrix # ST-88010A-1 PR 301030-A LIKE GLUE
        - Paul, Sean - Temperature; Breakout, 2005; SR-23227; Paul, Sean (Box 386)
        - Paul, Sean - We be burnin', 2005; SR-23228; Paul, Sean (Box 386)
          Catalog # PR 301772; A-side Matrix # COMMERCIAL 12" 0-93770 / PROMO 12" 301772-A PL BL BURNIN
        - Paul, Sean - Like glue, 2002; SR-23229; Paul, Sean (Box 386)
          Catalog # PROMO 70; A-side Matrix # PROMO 70 A LIKE GLUE
          VP Records
          Jamaica, New York
        - Paul Und Paula - You, you and me, 2001; SR-23230; Paul Und Paula (Box 386)
          Catalog # 74321 82645 1; A-side Matrix # B042822-01 A1 HL
          Electric Kingdom
        - Paul Und Paula - You, you and me, 2001; SR-23231; Paul Und Paula (Box 386)
        - Payne, Freda - I'll do anything for you, 1979; SR-23232; Payne, Freda (Box 386)
          In same jacket as # SR-23233. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # 8509; A-side Matrix # DISCO S-95237B G-1
          Capitol Records
        - Payne, Freda - I'll do anything for you, 1979; SR-23233; Payne, Freda (Box 386)
          In same jacket as # SR-23232. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Payne, Freda - Happy days are here again; Happy music (dance the night away), 1978; SR-23234; Payne, Freda (Box 386)
          Catalog # SPRO-8922; A-side Matrix # SPRO-8922 F1 (94275)
        - Payne, Freda - Red hot, 1979; SR-23235; Payne, Freda (Box 386)
          In same jacket as # SR-23236. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # SPRO-9219; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9219 (96102A) G-1
        - Payne, Freda - Red hot, 1979; SR-23236; Payne, Freda (Box 386)
          In same jacket as # SR-23235. 2 copies. Promo
        - Payton, Nicholas - Sonic trance'd, 2003; SR-23237; Payton, Nicholas (Box 386)
          Catalog # PRO-A-101249; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-101249 A/B SR-1
        - PBR StreetGang - You got me; Chemical pollution, 1985; SR-23238; PBR StreetGang (Box 386)
          Catalog # DM-85064; A-side Matrix # DM-85064-A1-
          Attic Sounds
        - PC Connection - Free from your love, 1998; SR-23239; PC Connection (Box 386)
          Catalog # PCR 04; A-side Matrix # HAL-127804-A
          Prince Charming
          South Beach, Florida
        - PD3 - Noisy music pt. II; Pass the mic, 1993; SR-23240; PD3; Points Proven; DJ Bizzness (Box 386)
          Catalog # PD002; A-side Matrix # PD 002 A1
          Payday Recordings
        - P.D.A. In Effect - Smoothe, 1987; SR-23241; P.D.A. In Effect (Box 386)
          Catalog # U.S.P. #150; A-side Matrix # USP-150 A
          Universal Sound Productions Inc.
        - Peaches & Herb - Let's fall in love, 1967; SR-23242; Peaches & Herb (Box 386)
          Catalog # TEM 3004; A-side Matrix # XLP116682-3E
          Date
        - Peaches & Herb - Freeway, 1981; SR-23243; Peaches & Herb (Box 386)
          Catalog # PRO 165; A-side Matrix # PRO 165 81 NP 5627 PW JS XTAL
        - Pearson, Dunn, Jr. - Go for the gusto, 1989; SR-23244; Pearson, Dunn, Jr.; Brown, Jocelyn (Box 386)
          Catalog # 9904-12; A-side Matrix # 9904-12A F/W CSB♪♪
          Compose
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Pearson, Renato - Soundmen on wax (optic vision), 1998; SR-23245; Pearson, Renato; JoVoon (Box 386)
          Catalog # SOW-421; A-side Matrix # SOW-421 A F/W RCE
          Soundmen On Wax
        - Pearson, Renato - Soundmen on wax (optic vision), 1998; SR-23246; Pearson, Renato; JoVoon (Box 386)
        - Peaston, David - Two wrongs (don't make it right), 1989; SR-23247; Peaston, David (Box 386)
          In same jacket as # SR-23248. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-21215; A-side Matrix # 0-21215-A-SR-1
        - Peaston, David - Two wrongs (don't make it right), 1989; SR-23248; Peaston, David (Box 386)
          In same jacket as # SR-23247. 2 copies.
        - Peaston, David - We're all in this together, 1989; SR-23249; Peaston, David (Box 386)
          Catalog # PRO-A-3947; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-3947-SR1 1-1
        - Pebblee-Poo - A fly guy, 1985; SR-23250; Pebblee-Poo (Box 386)
          Catalog # PRO-7083-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO 7083A
        - Pebbles - Are you ready?, 1995; SR-23251; Pebbles; Parental Advisory (Box 386)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3274; A-side Matrix # MCA-12348-A
        - Pebbles - Are you ready?, 1995; SR-23252; Pebbles; Parental Advisory (Box 386)
        - Pebbles - Backyard, 1990; SR-23253; Pebbles; Salt-N-Pepa (Box 386)
          Catalog # L33-1184; A-side Matrix # MCA-10470 FDS-1
        - Pebbles - Are you ready?, 1995; SR-23254; Pebbles; Parental Advisory (Box 386)
          Catalog # MCA12 55074; A-side Matrix # MCA-12350-A
        - Pebbles - Mercedes boy, 1988; SR-23255; Pebbles (Box 386)
          Catalog # MCA-23838; A-side Matrix # MCA 7562 FDS-6
        - Pebbles - Are you ready?, 1995; SR-23256; Pebbles; Parental Advisory (Box 386)
        - Pebbles - Love/hate (extended version); Axel f (12" version), 1987; SR-23257; Pebbles; Faltermeyer, Harold (Box 386)
          Catalog # MCA-23780; A-side Matrix # MCA-7099-FDS-2 FUTURE DISC
        - Pebbles - Do me right, 1988; SR-23258; Pebbles (Box 386)
          Catalog # L33-17586; A-side Matrix # MCA 8040 FDS-2 FUTURE DISC
        - Pebbles - Take your time, 1988; SR-23259; Pebbles (Box 386)
          Catalog # L33-17580; A-side Matrix # MCA 8020 FDS-1 FUTURE DISC
        - Pee Wee - Be my girl, 1982; SR-23260; Pee Wee; Ford, Pee Wee (Box 386)
          Catalog # SWRL 2202; A-side Matrix # SWRL 2202 A-RE
          Streetwise